

#### **Skills**

### **Basic**

JS (ES6+) TS HTML (Pug) CSS (Sass/Less)



#### **Frameworks**

Vue/Vuex React/Redux Three.js/A-Frame Node.js/Express



#### **Tools**

Devtools Git Webpack npm



## Languages

English — A2-B1 Russian — Native

# Contact

- Minsk, Belarus
- **a** +375 (33) 307-25-07
- ■ frants.mitskun@gmail.com
- in frantsm
- frantsmn
- ✓ frantsm
- @ frantsmn

# **FRANTS MITSKUN**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### Profile

Creative front-end developer with 3+ years of experience building interactive websites and components. I like to achieve smooth transitions and create 2D/3D animations. Also, I love to automate routine tasks and write modular, readable code

#### Experience

# **Creative Frontend Developer**

Egorov Agency · Full-time | Jun 2020 - Jul 2021 (1 yr 2 mos)

JS (ES6+), Vue/Vuex, Sass/Less, Pug, BEM, Bootstrap, Webpack, Prepros, Complex animations/interactions (Tween.js/GSAP), GLTF/GLB 3D Animations, Three.js, AR (A-Frame, Zappar) E-commerce projects (Laravel/Vue)

Various landings/promo/corporate websites with 3D models/animations (kitchen constructor, background animations, product presentation)

WebAR promo projects. Programming interactions and animations for characters and objects, fine-tuning of 3D object physical characteristics, creating custom controls for touch devices egorovagency.com

# **Frontend Developer**

Biggid · Part-time | Apr 2020 - Present · (1 yr 5 mos)

Vue/Vuex, React, Sass, Pug, BEM, Bootstrap, Grunt, Gulp E-commerce and booking project

UI prototyping. Booking widget and CRM system development. Work with open source components (Full Calendar, Input masks, pickers, sliders, animations, etc.)

biggid.com

# Frontend Developer, QA Engineer

DAROO · Full-time | Mar 2017 - Mar 2020 · (3 yrs)

HTML, CSS, SASS, JS (ES5, ES6+), JQuery, Handlebars.js, Gulp, Grunt, Bootstrap, Vue.is

Legacy support, Bug fixing

Content management tools development

E-mail letter constructor development

Site redesign. AMP/PWA. Developing new components and pages: main page, catalog, product card, partner card, main menu, blog pages, landing pages, admin panels

(2) daroo.by

# **Content Manager, QA Engineer**

DAROO · Full-time | Nov 2015 - Mar 2017 · (1 yr 5 mos)

HTML, CSS

Creating and updating existing content, Coding and sending Email letters, testing and analyzing new features and website

**3** daroo.by

 Data Entry Operator
 OSG Records Management · Part-time | Jun 2014 - Sep 2014 · (4 mos) Management of confidential data **©** osgrm.by

# Course

2018	JAVASCRIPT ADVANCED LEVEL IT Academy, Minsk
2015	SOFTWARE TESTING FUNDAMENTALS A1QA, Minsk

# Education

# • Engineer programmer economist

University of Management, Minsk | 2010 - 2015 Participation in the olympiad (C++, C#) Writing auxiliary teaching materials on the subjects: Visual Software application development (C#)